This could have been your hook.
Because when I see somebody wearing an
Apple Watch, really?
You burned 1,500 calories in an hour?
Well, he's right.
13 seconds, 13 seconds
that you got Sam Sulek there.
So if I know Sam,
I might wait to see whether
or not you're going to shout shit
about him. But if I don't know him,
I'm like, "Who the fuck are these guys?" I
think another thing here could have been
to establish yourself before this.
So let's say we're talking about fitness
trackers.
You should have established something
like,
"Our fitness tracker's a complete waste
of time. But before I answer that,
let's listen to what Sam Sulek has to
say."
Boom. Cut to the clip of Sam Sulek.
Then at least people know what they're
going to
get by being retained
and sitting through the Sulek video
because they go,
"Wow, I'm going to listen to Sam.
Then at the end,
I'm going to find out what
they're saying and some context about it."
And also by reacting to it with, "Well,
he's right," people now know your stance
on it.
So they might be like, "Oh, well, okay,
I'm leaving."
Well, a few years back,
Stanford did a study on seven different
fitness trackers.
This could have been your hook.
Stanford did a study on seven different
fitness
trackers to see whether or not they
were accurate.
But just before we get into that,
you may have seen this clip of Sam Sulek,
and
his stance was this. So let's find out
if he's correct.
Cut to the clip, Sam Sulek,
be in there talking back to it.
So what did the evidence say? Well.
The result, even the best
was off by almost 30%, and the worst
over-
SFX on this, tiny bit loud.
So I love the fact that you've got this
animation in there. I love
that we've got a little sound to it.
If it was too quiet, not a problem, but
if it's too loud, it's a problem.
Now, they are good for tracking steps
and heart rate, but calories, nah.
But that doesn't matter because you
shouldn't be worried about how many
calories
you are burning in a single workout.
In fact,
it only accounts for about 10% of your
daily calorie burn.
But we'll save that for another video.
Love that. Love that. Save
that for another video.
Oh,
this guy's going to be putting out loads
of content.
He didn't beg me for a follow.
He just said he's going to save it for
another
video.
I'm going to follow this guy because he
put across a very
smart point. I liked it.
I like what he's about.
I'm going to follow this guy.
I'm going to support him. Dash.